startingelectronics.org 2018-08-16

# Privacy Policy

**Starting Electronics Needs Your Help!**  
It is that time of the year when we need to pay for web hosting and buy new components and equipment for new tutorials. You can help by making a donation. Contribute to this website by clicking the **Donate** button. The total will be updated once daily. (You may need to clear your browser cache to see the updates.)

**Target Amount: $2000**  
**Amount Raised: $1159**

Donations Received

**Top Donor: C.C. $100**

X

Home  Site Privacy Policy 

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us from our contact form.

At startingelectronics.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information received and collected by startingelectronics.org and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, startingelectronics.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

startingelectronics.org does not use cookies. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie and Web Beacons

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:  
Google Adsense  
amazon.com  
amazon.co.uk

Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on user's prior visits to startingelectronics.org.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on user's visits to startingelectronics.org and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising opt-out page at http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/.

Users may visit those websites to opt out of cookies (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). You can opt out of some, but not all, of these cookies in one location at the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out website at www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
